goldenplec.com 2017-12-22

# Privacy Policy - GoldenPlec Music Magazine

## Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us. At [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our blogging products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our [Administrator](mailto:admin@goldenplec.com).

It is [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/)’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/)’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/)’s visitors use its website. From time to time, [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

[GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on articles. [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/)’s websites choose to interact with [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) in ways that require [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account to comment to provide a username and email address. [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/). [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

[GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites. For instance, [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) may monitor the most popular posts on [Goldenplec](https://www.goldenplec.com/).com or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, [GoldenPlec](https://www.goldenplec.com/) does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

GoldenPlec discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on GoldenPlec’s behalf or to provide services available at GoldenPlec’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organisations may be located outside of your home country; by using GoldenPlec’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. GoldenPlec will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations, as described above, GoldenPlec discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when GoldenPlec believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of GoldenPlec, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a GoldenPlec mailing list and have supplied your email address, GoldenPlec may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with GoldenPlec and our products. We primarily use our various mailing lists to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. GoldenPlec takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorised access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. GoldenPlec uses cookies to help GoldenPlec identify and track visitors, their usage of GoldenPlec website, and their website access preferences. GoldenPlec visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using GoldenPlec’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of GoldenPlec’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

This is implied acceptance of the cookies as per the EU Cookie Directive. Implied consent is hereby granted by use of the site.

### Business Transfers

If GoldenPlec, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that GoldenPlec goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of GoldenPlec may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognise your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by GoldenPlec and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

In the case of Muzu video adverts, cookies may be used to remember a users choices on our site. If you mute the video or advert, it will remember this and keep all Muzu content muted for you from then on in.

### Comments

Comments and other content submitted to our Akismet anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, GoldenPlec may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in GoldenPlec’s sole discretion. GoldenPlec encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a WordPress.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
